yeah from the Midwest moved to the city
I got hit by a car immediately
we did yeah I got hit yeah just crossing
the street because growing up in the
woods you don't look both ways
there's no traffic it's dirt roads so I
had the woods mentality moved to the
city this is what happened I was hanging
out with some friends and I was like oh
I gotta go you guys there's my there's
the bus I gotta catch this bus I'll see
you later and I went to walk the bus
stop was on the other side of the street
and I just I just walked to the bus stop
I didn't think I just walked straight to
it and then I remember I got in the
middle of the road I was like all right
you're supposed to look so I looked and
I just saw a Honda Civic
headed my way and I did that oop noise I
went up
[Laughter]
you know that oop noise but you don't
know what I just go look and then
everything went dark
that's all I remember going oh black
and then I wake up and I'm just laying
in the road
and I popped up and the bus was at the
bus stop and you know when you're on bus
catching mode
remember that was doesn't matter
so I just popped up with
wood and I hobbled
and I still got onto the bus I swiped my
car I got a window seat everything's
looking good and I sit down and the bus
doesn't move and then I look out the
window and there's about 30 people all
on the sidewalk looking at me
specifically
and I was like what's going on I don't
even know what happened and then I said
my friend comes running across the
street and he gets under the bus he goes
Jeffy you gotta get off the bus man we
all saw you get hit by that car you flew
into the air pretty sure you're in shock
right now
there's an ambulance on the way and I
was like an ambulance that's gonna cost
a lot more on this bus
on an ambulance money I'm a bus guy
that's right stood up I look behind me
and everybody on the bus just looking at
me wide-eyed because they're just on
their way home and then they see a guy
get hit and then still get on Just Like
Mondays can you believe it
[Applause]
oh boy
my friend we got off we're gonna go back
across the street and he takes me to the
bathroom goes you gotta clean up and I
look in the mirror and there's just
blood all over my face
just oh it's just all blood that's like
Cody am I okay and he was like nobody
knows foreign
so the ambulance shows up and I'm
talking to him I was like I don't have
any health insurance can I not go I feel
okay I'm trying to talk my way out of it
I'm like no you gotta oh come on let's
go so they gave me the ambulance and I'm
sitting in the aimless then we're on the
way to the hospital and remember this
there's an older guy with a mustache
she's got the clipboard and he goes did
I over here you don't have any health
insurance I was like hey I got nothing
I'm freaking out then he goes well
we can't bill you if you give me a fake
name
[Laughter]
so what's your name
and my name is Jeff she ET and I went is
Jeff shine
that was the best I could think of any
anybody was like isn't that your name
and I was like it's close but no he's
like how about we just call you Jeff
Adams I was like you can call me
whatever you want as long as this is
free call me Betty I don't care
so we get to the hospital and he grabs
Me by their shoulders and he goes
remember you're Jeff Adams
good luck
like I'm getting ready for an audition
like thanks Dan I'm not gonna dance so I
walk into the hospital I was like hi I
got hit by a car and I'm Jeff Adams
shut up
that's all I have for this character so
far I'm still working on it
and they're like oh I have a seat we'll
come get you in a minute we'll take you
in the back room so they finally they
take me in the back room the doctor sign
signs will light in my eyes and he's
like well I don't see a concussion so
that's good but how about you go back to
the waiting room we'll get you in a
second to give you a CAT scan to make
sure your brain's not bleeding so I'm
sitting in the waiting room and I'm
freaking out at a CAT scan they might
figure out who I am I don't know they're
looking in here I'm not smart
so I'm sitting there on the same day he
walks out you know
walks by and he goes hey come outside
with me real quick so we go outside and
he goes do you have a concussion or
anything what's going on and I was like
they want to give me a cast scan to make
sure my brain's not bleeding so I don't
know man and he's like the answer that
happening is like one in a million They
Don't Know Who You Are
says get out of here
so I just left
when I got home my roommate was like
what happened to you and I was like I
got hit by a car and I just snuck out of
the hospital
I'm gonna go to bed wish me luck
and I made it thank you very much you
guys hey thanks for watching and
download the dry bar comedy app and use
promo code Jeff Sheen